A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Advanced Medical Fellowships, SG 1, Series 3 FA275
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Awards in the Health Field, 1933-1978; 2
  - Schedl, Harold P., October 14, 1964 to September 13, 1968; June 22, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 460)
  - Schein, Arnold H., November 5, 1962-May 24, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 461)
  - Scheinberg, Israel Herbert, September 20, 1962-March 8, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 462)
  - Schilling, Robert F., June 18, 1958-December 4, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 463)
  - Scholes, Robert T., December 14, 1952-December 26, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 464)
  - Schur, Max, February 21, 1963-April 8, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 465)
  - Schwartz, Herbert C., June 29, 1965 to January 26, 1967; March 30, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 466)
  - Schwartz, Samuel S., November 2, 1945-October 15, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 467)
  - Scoville, Mildred C., January 28, 1965-February 16, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 468)
  - Scudder, John, October 17, 1937-September 25, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 469)
  - Seaman, William B., April 13, 1964-December 21, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 470)
  - Segal, Harry L., August 14, 1962 to April 22, 1963; April 20, 1964 to February 2, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 471)
  - Senn, Milton J. E., January 11, 1951 to October 31, 1951; September 10, 1957 to January 24, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 472)
  - Shadle, Oscar W., October 18, 1948-February 1, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 473)
  - Shaffer, Morris F., April 23, 1963-June 7, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 474)
  - Shands, Harley C., February 15, 1957-June 29, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 475)
  - Shands, Harley C., February 15, 1957-June 29, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 476)
  - Shands, Harley C., February 15, 1962-October 23, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 477)
  - Shands, Harley C., February 15, 1962-October 23, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 478)
  - Sheehan, Donal, April 25, 1962-July 20, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 479)
  - Sheline, Glenn E., November 23, 1965-March 4, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 480)
  - Shemin, David, May 6, 1964-November 6, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 481)
  - Shinowara, George Y., October 21, 1965-February 7, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 482)
  - Shirley, Hale F., November 11, 1954-November 12, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 483)
  - Shull, Harrison J., April 21, 1946-October 1, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 484)
  - Shulman, Sidney, January 20, 1965-April 26, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 485)
  - Silen, William, January 5, 1965-February 4, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 486)
  - Sims, Ethan Allen H., August 30, 1963-September 7, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 487)
  - Skinner, James C., July 5, 1961-June 9, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 488)
  - Slade, Hutton D., May 22, 1963-July 10, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 489)
  - Smith College, October 10, 1947-January 20, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 490)
  - Smith, Donald C., April 20, 1951-April 16, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 491)
  - Smith, Francis L., May 24, 1955-March 29, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 492)
  - Smith, Richard T., March 23, 1965-September 20, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 493)
  - Snoke, Albert W. and Parnie Snoke, July 5, 1969-January 23, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 494)
  - Sobel, Edna H., April 4, 1947 to November 2, 1949; November 28, 1961 to February 15, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 495)
  - Sobel, Edna H., April 4, 1947 to November 2, 1949; November 28, 1961 to February 15, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 496)
  - Sodeman, W. A., August 19, 1937 to March 17, 1941; December 19, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 497)
  - Sottong, Phillip, April 18, 1951 to April 5, 1957; March 31, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 498)
  - Sottong, Phillip, April 18, 1951 to April 5, 1957; March 31, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 499)
  - Spellman, Mitchell W., February 19, 1951-June 13, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 500)
  - Sprague, Charles C., July 11, 1950 to December 1, 1952; October 24, 1963 to January 19, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 501)
  - Squire, Lucy Frank, March 28, 1961-September 16, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 502)
  - Stamey, Thomas A., August 3, 1966-June 17, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 503)
  - Stara, Jerry F., April 10, 1954-July 7, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 504)
  - State, David, January 22, 1964-December 23, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 505)
  - Stead, Eugene A., Jr., January 16, 1967-March 27, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 506)
  - Steinbach, Howard L., April 23, 1963-March 10, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 507)
  - Stern, Joseph R., September 24, 1959-March 21, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 508)
  - Stetten, Dewitt, Jr., October 25, 1962-November 20, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 509)
  - Stevens, Kingsley M., December 2, 1964-Steptember 30, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 510)
  - Stevenson, Ian, March 28, 1961-September 29, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 511)
  - Stotz, Elmer H., November 6, 1961-October 23, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 512)
  - Stowell, Robert Eugene, November 8, 1945 to April 5, 1949; June 12-16, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 513)
  - Stracher, Alfred, October 4, 1965-November 21, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 514)
  - Streeter, George A., February 14, 1948-September 11, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 515)
  - Stricker, Fred L., October 5, 1948-July 16, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 516)
  - Strominger, Jack L., October 19, 1954-April 13, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 517)
  - Sutliff, Wheelan D., December 2, 1943-November 1, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 518)
  - Swank, Roy L., January 27, 1939 to May 8, 1952; June 23, 1960 to October 28, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 519)
  - Swank, Roy L., January 27, 1939 to May 8, 1952; June 23, 1960 to October 28, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 520)
  - Sweet, Norman J., June 28, 1961-December 19, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 521)
  - Sweet, William H., March 11, 1940-June 2, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 522)
  - Tagiuri, Renato, July 8, 1953-October 27, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 523)
  - Tallman, Frank Ford, November 24, 1959-December 15, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 524)
  - Taussig, Helen B., October 6, 1958-June 15, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 525)
  - Taylor, John Fuller, August 11, 1960-February 13, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 526)
  - Taylor, Keith B., January 15, 1965-March 10, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 527)
  - Telford, Ira R., March 3, 1966-September 13, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 528)
  - Thomas, Lewis, July 10, 1956 to March 19, 1958; February 12, 1959 to March 25, 1959; February 27, 1962 to July 1, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 529)
  - Thompson, Ian Murchie, March 27, 1964-February 7, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 530)
  - Thompson, Richard F., April 28, 1965-March 30, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 531)
  - Thorup, Oscar A., January 2, 1959-March 14, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 532)
  - Tichell, Robert H., July 15, 1964-October 15, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 533)
  - Tiffany, Elberton J., January 26, 1942-January 21, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 534)
  - Tobin, Charles E., December 3, 1963-July 29, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 535)
  - Tobin, Joseph M., January 4, 1960-September 8, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 536)
  - Towery, Beverly T., September 29, 1941-December 20, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 537)
  - Tsuboi, Kenneth K., August 6, 1965-September 22, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 538)
  - Turner, Joseph C., February 17, 1939-January 22, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 539)
  - Uhr, Jonathan, February 1, 1960-May 27, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 540)
  - Unna, Klaus R. W., December 16, 1964-January 4, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 541)
  - Venable, John, November 24, 1937 to February 7, 1941; February 11, 1953 to January 1, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 542)
  - Waelsch, Heinrich B., June 1, 1961-March 28, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 543)
  - Waggoner, Raymond W., July 12, 1963-June 29, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 544)
  - Walford, Roy L., August 10, 1966-November 3, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 545)
  - Walker, James E. C., February 19, 1965-March 17, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 546)
  - Walker, James E. C., February 19, 1965-March 17, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 547)
  - Walker, Sheppard M., June 23, 1961-February 25, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 548)
  - Wallace, Helen M., February 11, 1965-April 17, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 549)
  - Wang, Shih-Chun, June 18, 1965-April 11,1968 (Box 45, Folder 550)
  - Warren, Leonard, November 26, 1962-December 22, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 551)
  - Waser, Peter, January 13, 1969-April 8, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 552)
  - Watson, Cecil J., November 20, 1952 to December 19, 1961; January 4, 1967 to December 7, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 553)
  - Watson, Janet, November 6, 1942 to November 11, 1946; July 11-17, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 554)
  - Weens, Heinz Stephen, November 6, 1942 to November 5, 1947; October 1, 1958 to June 29, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 555)
  - Weinerman, E. Richard, December 30, 1964-July 18, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 556)
  - Welch, Arnold D., December 10, 1963-October 1, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 557)
  - Welt, Louis G., April 9, 1962 to December 14, 1964; October 7, 1968 to June 15, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 558)
  - Werkman, Sidney L., June 16, 1963-February 24, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 559)
  - White, Abraham, July 29, 1963-September 30, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 560)
  - White, Abraham, July 29, 1963-September 30, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 561)
  - White, Abraham, December 18, 1970-January 4, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 562)
    Report - December 9, 1970.
  - White, Abraham, December 18, 1970-January 4, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 563)
  - White, Kerr L., April 4, 1958-July 1, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 564)
  - Whitehorn, John Clare, July 20, 1959-August 27, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 565)
  - Whitridge, John, Jr., August 10, 1959-September 18,1961 (Box 47, Folder 566)
  - Whittier, John R., December 6, 1950-January 10, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 567)
  - Wiecking, David K., January 5, 1966-July 25, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 568)
  - Wilkins, Lawson, August 10, 1961-May 28, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 569)
  - Wilson, David H., April 27, 1956-April 5, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 570)
  - Wilson, T. Hastings, September 15, 1964-January 9, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 571)
  - Winters, Robert W., November 18, 1965-April 17, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 572)
  - Winzler, Richard J., November 13, 1957-July 17, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 573)
  - Wise, Burton Louis, February 12, 1965-October 14, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 574)
  - Wissler, Robert W., February 28, 1962-January 4, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 575)
  - Wolf, George A., March 14, 1961-December 13, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 576)
  - Wolf, Stewart, September 19, 1962-July 8, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 577)
  - Wood, Earl Howard, November 2, 1964-April 2, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 578)
  - Wood, Harland G., January 30, 1961-November 4, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 579)
  - Wool, Ira G., November 16, 1955-February 20, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 580)
  - Wortis, Samuel Bernard, May 15, 1963-August 24, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 581)
  - Wright, Stanley W., January 14, 1958 to May 5, 1960; July 28, 1965 to October 2, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 582)
  - Wright, Stanley W., January 14, 1958 to May 5, 1960; July 28, 1965 to October 2, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 583)
  - Wyngaarden, James B., April 6, 1962-February 23, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Yang, Jen Tsi, November 2, 1965-February 16, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Yingling, Doris B., September 29, 1954-December 11, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 586)
  - Zamecnik, Paul Charles, January 3, 1961-February 26, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 587)
  - Ziskind, Morton, March 12, 1948-December 29, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 588)
  - Zubin, Joseph, October 10, 1956-June 30, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 589)
  - Zuspan, Frederick P., November 25, 1968-November 20, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 590)
  - Zwerling, Israel, August 4, 1965-April 10, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 591)
- Foreign Fellowships, 1941-1980; 3
  This subseries is arranged alphabetically by fellow. The material within each fellow's file is arranged chronologically.
  This subseries contains correspondence, financial data, and reports.
  - Aas, Knut, July 14, 1954-November 6, 1958; December 22, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 592)
  - Affleck, J. W., April 7, 1965-July 5, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 593)
  - Amundsen, Egil, February 28, 1964-January 5, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 594)
  - Andrew, Richard R., October 4, 1961-February 25, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 595)
  - Aterman, Kurt, December 15, 1947 to February 18, 1953; November 25 to December 2, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 596)
  - Audu, I. S., March 1, 1964-March 30, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 597)
  - Awoliyi, Elizabeth A., September 12, 1962-September 1, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 598)
  - Bataliwalla, Bapai, January 25, 1949-December 13, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 599)
  - Bennett, F. John, January 30, 1962-November 28, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 600)
  - Bethune, John E., December 15, 1955-November 7, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 601)
  - Biggart, J. Henry, October 30, 1963-October 5, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 602)
  - Bjorneboe, Mogens, March 3, 1948-January 16, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 603)
  - Blomfield, G. W., November 24, 1947-April 9, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 604)
  - Boman, Kurt, December 16, 1965-September 14, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 605)
  - Boquet, Paul, January 14, 1948-July 14, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 606)
  - Boquet, Paul, January 14, 1948-July 14, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 607)
  - Bowlby, John, June 7, 1966-January 11, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 608)
  - Boyo, Alexander E., December 20, 1962-November 13, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 609)
  - Byrne, Patrick S., April 22, 1966-January 13, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 610)
  - Camber, Bernard, November 29, 1948-April 2, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 611)
  - Carey, H. M., July 27, 1962-November 24, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 612)
  - Carstairs, George Morrison, February 12, 1959-May 15, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 613)
  - Cervantes, Esther Leah, April 18, 1951-January 19, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 614)
  - Chang, Katharine Feng-yi, April 15, 1950-February 28, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 615)
  - Cook, Harold F., January 5, 1962-March 17, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 616)
  - Cox, Robert, January 5, 1962-March 16, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 617)
  - Crawford, M. A., April 29, 1964-December 15, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 618)
  - Crock, Gerard W., May 26, 1961-July 17, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 619)
  - Croxatto, Oscar C., October 21, 1950-July 11, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 620)
  - Dagher, Fuad, June 8, 1961-October 3, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 621)
  - Dahlgren, Sven, February 13, 1967-May 1, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 622)
  - De, Tran-dinh, November 11, 1949-October 2, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 623)
  - Del Mundo, Fe, June 20, 1963 to December 13, 1966; August 8-15, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 624)
  - Denk, Wolfgang, December 10, 1947-June 22, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 625)
  - Desai, Manu [Manu Mehta/Manu Joshi], July 6, 1949-March 16, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 626)
  - Dewhurst, C. J., March 24, 1964-November 23, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 627)
  - Dhaveloose, Mariette Francine [Mrs. Jacques Pliner], May 4, 1952-June 26, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 628)
  - Dixon, Andrew D., January 13, 1961-April 1, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 629)
  - Duncan, Archibald S., March 7, 1967-July 4, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 630)
  - Duncan, J. W. Kwame, April 13, 1965-May 9, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 631)
  - Eickhoff, Louise F. W., March 20, 1950-December 15, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 632)
  - Elebute, Oyinade, November 20, 1962-January 10, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 633)
  - Elek, Stephen D., October 19, 1961-December 13, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 634)
  - Ellis, Hugh, May 28, 1965-February 20, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 635)
  - Ellis, John R., February 3, 1959-November 26, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 636)
  - Evans, John, November 16, 1967-October 25, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 637)
  - Fawcett, Peter G., January 15, 1963-June 3, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 638)
  - Felluga, Bruno, December 9, 1964-July 10, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 639)
  - Fitzgerald, Oliver, January 15, 1963-October 11, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 640)
  - Flavier, Juan, April 27, 1966 to September 1, 1967; March 14, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 641)
  - Fraenkel, Gustav Julius, October 4, 1961-OCtober 17, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 642)
  - Galbraith, J. E. K., September 6, 1963-December 21, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 643)
  - Gale, Ernest F., March 7, 1950-July 30, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 644)
  - Gardner, Frances, October 4, 1961-February 27, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 645)
  - Gibbons, James L., June 28, 1964-June 14, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 646)
  - Gibson, Ian, June 21, 1963-April 16, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 647)
  - Goldberg, Ian J. L., October 22, 1962-January 14, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 648)
  - Gore, Phyllis, October 20, 1950-June 30, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 649)
  - Graves, John C., March 7, 1967-April 9, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 650)
  - Grontoft, Otto, October 30, 1967-March 28, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 651)
  - Hallgrimsson, Jonas, February 13, 1967-March 3, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 652)
  - Hay, John D., October 30, 1963-June 30, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 653)
  - Heller, Hans, November 5, 1948-January 25, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 654)
  - Helsingen, Nils, December 16, 1965-January 20, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 655)
  - Henderson, John L., January 15, 1963-August 27, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 656)
  - Henson, Ronald A., May 21, 1964-January 5, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 657)
  - Hetzel, Basil Stuart, February 25, 1964-April 15, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 658)
  - Humerfelt, Sigurd, February 13, 1967-December 15, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 659)
  - Hunter, Robert Brockie, August 16, 1959-January 11, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 660)
  - International Society for Cell Biology (7th International Congress), December 14, 1948-December 4, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 661)
  - Itzkovitz, Hanna, February 21, 1949-November 14, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 662)
  - Jason, Hilliard, June 25, 1956 to October 29, 1958; June 19, 1961 to April 29, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 663)
  - Jepson, R. P., September 24, 1963-November 26, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 664)
  - Jessop, William J. E., October 4, 1961-August 29, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 665)
  - Johnstone, Robert Maxwell, January 15, 1963-January 21, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 666)
  - Jones, A. Trevor, December 21, 1962-October 3, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 667)
  - Jones, Maxwell Shaw, January 20, 1959-August 8, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 668)
  - Joske, Richard A., November 29, 1954-November 29, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 669)
  - Juel-Nielsen, Niels, February 24, 1967-February 20, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 670)
  - Jurzynska, Zoja, May 30, 1950-March 2, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 671)
  - Kay, Won Chuel, July 20, 1964-September 8, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 672)
  - Kemp, Thomas A., March 15, 1967-August 6, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 673)
  - Khaddouri, Joseph, January 10, 1952-June 28, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 674)
  - Khuri, Raja, February 27, 1968-May 13, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 675)
  - Kilpatrick, Robert, October 4, 1961-December 2, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 676)
  - Knight, Peter R., July 5, 1966-October 3, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 677)
  - Knight, Robert K., February 15, 1963-May 22, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 678)
  - Konno, Kiyoshi, January 20, 1965-September 25, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 679)
  - Lander, Harry, September 11, 1964-January 21, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 680)
  - Lee, Kyu Won, September 22, 1964-July 3, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 681)
  - Lefroy, Richard Bruce, January 12, 1961-May 11, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 682)
  - Lennox, Bernard, October 4, 1961-August 27, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 683)
  - Leon, Carlos A., October 11, 1963-October 16, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 684)
  - Levy, Emmanuel, April 26, 1965-May 23, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 685)
  - Lewis, Anthony A. G., October 30, 1963-August 29, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 686)
  - MacDonald, William B., February 28, 1963-July 5, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 687)
  - Madsen, Joop J. V., December 16, 1965-December 19, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 688)
  - Magarey, J. R., January 15, 1963-January 5, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 689)
  - Malins, John M., October 30, 1963-September 21, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 690)
  - Malkani, Parvati K., September 20, 1961-January 14, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 691)
  - Marmasse, Claude J. L., July 8, 1963-June 14, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 692)
  - Martens, Sten G. R., October 17, 1955-May 29, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 693)
  - Martin, Frederick Morris, January 13, 1961-September 11, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 694)
  - Marshall, Vernon C., June 22, 1961-September 15, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 695)
  - McCarthy, William H., November 20, 1964-August 3, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 696)
  - McCrie, John Gibb, December 23, 1958-January 13, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 697)
  - Mensink, Elizabeth, April 23, 1955-January 10, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 698)
  - Meyrick, R. L., March 15, 1967-November 17, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 699)
  - Mickerson, John N., December 16, 1964-December 23, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 700)
  - Middlemiss, J. H., October 30, 1963-April 22, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 701)
  - Milton, Gerald W., September 21, 1965-February 27, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 702)
  - Morfini, Lela, April 18, 1951-February 25, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 703)
  - Mortimer, Kingsley E., October 24, 1963-October 8, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 704)
  - Murray, James G., May 13, 1965-November 19, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 705)
  - Naeraa, Noe, October 26, 1967-July 11, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 706)
  - Nash, Denis F. Ellison, October 4, 1961-April 10, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 707)
  - Natori, Tomi, March 10, 1950-September 29, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 708)
  - Nelms, John Douglas, December 16, 1965-August 9, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 709)
  - Nichols, Florence L., February 24, 1961-December 17, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 710)
  - Nichols, Florence L., January 5, 1953-April 10, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 711)
  - Njoku-Obi, Augustine Nwaneri, April 3, 1964 to May 29, 1964; July 29 to September 9, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 712)
  - Nurcombe, Barry, December 21, 1962-June 20, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 713)
  - Oguntolu, O. A., February 28, 1964-September 10, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 714)
  - Opit, Louis J., May 10, 1961-December 30, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 715)
  - Oren, Joseph, May 11, 1955-October 29, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 716)
  - O'Sullivan, Denis J., January 15, 1963-November 1, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 717)
  - Owen, Samuel Griffith, December 18, 1963-September 7, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 718)
  - Pain, A. Bernard, January 15, 1963-December 31, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 719)
  - Paloheimo, Martti, June 14, 1950 to July 14, 1953; November 12, 1956 to January 3, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 720)
  - Palva, Ilmari, December 1, 1967-March 25, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 721)
  - Papara, Dora K., April 5, 1951 to November 4, 1953; April 13, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 722)
  - Papoulacos, Michael N., March 29, 1948-June 29, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 723)
  - Parker, Norma, November 9, 1943-January 30, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 724)
  - Paulley, John W., April 22, 1966 to May 1, 1968; February 24-27, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 725)
  - Pickles, Vernon R., May 29, 1963-August 10, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 726)
  - Pickles, W. N., January 21, 1948-February 13, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 727)
  - Raska, Karel, April 23, 1965-January 16, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 728)
  - Read, John Robert, March 31, 1964-May 12, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 729)
  - Reid, J. V. O., October 30, 1963-March 3, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 730)
  - Reid, Ross T. W., January 15, 1963-September 6, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 731)
  - Rickham, P. P., January 23, 1951 to May 16, 1952; August 17-28, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 732)
  - Rodger, T. Ferguson, February 17, 1950 to December 1, 1954; January 17, 1956 to March 19, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 733)
  - Roughton, F. J. W., July 7, 1941-April 16, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 734)
  - Rowe, Frances, July 9, 1954-July 25, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 735)
  - Rowley, Derrick, June 25, 1963-February 25, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 736)
  - Russell, James Knox, January 13, 1961-February 27, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 737)
  - Sadka, Marie, July 9, 1956-November 29, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 738)
  - Saint, Eric C., December 30, 1954-March 22, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 739)
  - Saint, Eric C., December 30, 1954-March 22, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 740)
  - Sauser, Gustav, December 10, 1947-March 15, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 741)
  - Schutzenberger, Marcel-Paul, July 11, 1961-November 19, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 742)
  - Sen, Kamala, April 20, 1950-January 14, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 743)
  - Shakhashiri, Zekin A., December 27, 1957-February 6, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 744)
  - Sheehan, John Denis, November 1, 1963-October 17, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 745)
  - Shehadeh, Isam H., March 22, 1966-December 5, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 746)
  - Shepherd, Michael, January 13, 1961-December 14, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 747)
  - Short, Coralie Rendle, January 15, 1963-November 4, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 748)
  - Simmonds, W. J., November 28, 1963-November 5, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 749)
  - Sjoberg, Liv Grannes, August 19, 1948-November 15, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 750)
  - Smart, George Algernon, October 25, 1960-March 11, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 751)
  - Smith, Adam N., November 1, 1962-April 14, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 752)
  - Spillane, J. D., October 14, 1958 to January 13, 1961; June 1-14, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 753)